<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-11-20T02:39:53+00:00</updated><id>https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Shawn, But With a “W”</title><subtitle>I&apos;ll think of something later </subtitle><entry><title type="html">i fogor</title><link href="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2024/i-fogor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="i fogor"/><published>2024-11-19T18:22:39+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-19T18:22:39+00:00</updated><id>https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2024/i-fogor</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2024/i-fogor/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="whats-been-happening">What’s Been Happening?</h1> <p>In simple words, I forgot.</p> <p>I somehow just managed to forget about both the existence of this page and how to use jekyll.</p> <h1 id="now-what">Now What?</h1> <p>Going back to tutorial hell trying to figure out how to use this thing.</p> <p>I will finally add the projects to the project page (no promises).</p> <h1 id="more-notes">More Notes</h1> <p>Ok I just tried to commit this and the page is not showing this blog time for half an hour of debugging nothing.</p> <p>I’ll also try making a copy of the “creating this site” blog and see what happens.</p> <p>Ok coming back to this, the copy exists in the blog but this doesn’t. Why? Watch it be some stupidly obvious reason I never realised.</p> <p>I think I might just nuke this thing and start from scratch.</p> <p>Never mind I woke up the second day and pushed a commit and it works now?</p> <p>Turns out I just had to trust to process.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="rants"/><category term="placeholder-tag"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[what am i doing]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">creating this site</title><link href="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2023/creating-this-site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="creating this site"/><published>2023-08-10T20:43:04+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-10T20:43:04+00:00</updated><id>https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2023/creating-this-site</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://shawn-but-with-a-w.github.io/blog/2023/creating-this-site/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="context">Context</h1> <p>I’ve been thinking about making my own website for quite a while.</p> <p>Before actually making this site, I’ve made a couple local webpages for school (which I will put in the projects page if I do remember) and an <a href="https://softwarecats.github.io/">organisation page</a> with Github pages using HTML and CSS. I finally touched a bit JS in creating the n-body simulation for school recently.</p> <p>Out of familiarity and being broke, Github pages was my hosting choice once again. Trying out something new as an excuse for being lazy, I tried Jekyll to turn markdown into webpages.</p> <h1 id="implementation">Implementation</h1> <p>It was not worth it. I probably would’ve been better of had I started from scratch again.</p> <p>I read through very long documentation and the Github guide on installing Jekyll. After running into a few problems with the command line it was eventually all sorted and I had a working site locally that was soon deployed but Github sites.</p> <p>And then I realised I could’ve just stolen someone else’s template for Jekyll.</p> <p>After deleting the repository, creating a new one from the template and then carefully walking through the README (I have dyslexia if you can’t tell already), I ran into a problem where the site would not deploy. The problem was made even worse by the command line producing errors when I try to host the site locally.</p> <p>So back to the drawing board again, and the repository was swiftly deleted and created once more. Being scarred by previous experiences I made very small commits and stared at the action tab as the site was deployed for every commit. I think the reason for the site not deploying was because I commented out some stuff which made it unhappy.</p> <p>Anyhow after many hours of making slight changes, pushing, deploying and checking the site, it seems to be functioning despite the amount of unnecessary bytes in the repository.</p> <h1 id="what-now">What Now?</h1> <p>I’ll probably display some projects and repos to this site, maybe use it to host my markdown notes if I ever figure that out.</p> <p>I’ve also become surprisingly familiar with command line git because of writing way too many commits for this site.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="rants"/><category term="placeholder-tag"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[(complaining) about the process of creating this site]]></summary></entry></feed>